Brayan Sanchez

Software Developer

leon16.bs@gmail.com | spiegell.live | +57 3183899776

EXPERIENCE

Aventi Solutions — Back-end developer

APRIL 2023 - PRESENT | CALI, COLOMBIA

Develop Ecommerce sites built with Magento to national and international companies. Implemented improvements in the JavaScript development optimizing the code by 20% and enhanced the use of Docker.

Universidad del Valle — Software Developer

APRIL 2022 - JANUARY 2023 | CALI, COLOMBIA

Improved the design and functionality of the university's software for students and professors, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript y PHP.

Abbott — *Intern*

JUNE 2017 - JUNE 2018 | CALI, COLOMBIA

Performed administrative tasks as an office assistant.

PROJECTS

E-commerce Lottus

Electronic commerce built with React, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL and Docker. Implements user authentication, product catalog, shopping cart, checkout and wishlist. It s deployed in GCP.

Task manager

Web app built with Node.js, Express, EJS, PostgreSQL and Docker that manages the day-to-day tasks. Implements user authentication.

Weather app

Web app built with React, JavaScript and Tailwind that provides weather information of any city using the OpenWeatherMap API.

SUMMARY

Software Developer with 1 year of experience developing scalable and user-friendly web applications.

SKILLS

Programming languages

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, PostgreSQL

Technologies

React, Next, Docker, Linux, Express, Material UI, Jest, GCP

Tools

Git, GitHub, Jira, Notion, Asana, Slack

EDUCATION

Universidad del Valle

AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT Systems engineering student

CECEP

AUGUST 2016 - JANUARY 2020 Industrial Technologist